http://www.discovery-solutions.com/privacypolicy

Discovery Solutions International (DSI)
Privacy Notice
It is our goal to make your experience as a customer of DSI or visitor to www.discovery-solutions.com as enjoyable as possible. We also respect your privacy and will protect that privacy for all our visitors and customers. To that end, we have established several rules to make you feel secure and comfortable when visiting our site and working with us. We also certify that our privacy practices satisfy the European Union Safe Harbor principles as set forth by the Canada’s Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act. The privacy policies described on this page apply to all visitors to this site and DSI customers unless we have a contract with you that specifically provides for different privacy measures.
Personal Information
When you visit our site, you do so anonymously. We may, however, gather information on the length of your stay, the pages you view, and your movement patterns through the site. We collect this information solely for our internal use. The ultimate goal for collecting this information is to make the site better and, in turn, make it a more enjoyable experience for you and all our visitors.
When you do business with us or visit certain areas of this site, we may ask for personal information from you, such as your name, mailing address, email address, credit card number, etc. Providing this information is absolutely voluntary on your part. We use the information you provide to send you brochures, allow you access to certain areas of the site, establish email contact with you, and process your requests. We may use this information within DSI and with our business partners who have agreed to adhere to DSI ’s privacy standards, but we will not sell or give this information to others. If you refuse to provide such information when requested, you may not be able to access certain areas of this site or purchase DSI products or services.
You may view and correct any personal information you have submitted to us by requesting this information from DSI ’s webmaster. You may also access and correct your personal information by writing to DSI , #33 – 3030 Sunridge Way, Calgary, Alberta;
Attn: Privacy Officer. If you write to us, please provide your name, mailing address and a clear description of the information you wish to view or correct. When you submit personal information to DSI you understand and agree that such information may be transmitted across national boundaries and may be stored in DSI facilities in Canada or other countries.
Cookies and Hypertext Links
We use cookies and hypertext links throughout www.discovery-solutions.com to improve the quality of your visit to our site. You can always choose to turn off the cookies' functionality within your browser, but it may detract from the quality of your visit to www.discovery-solutions.com (with cookies turned off, you may, for example, be asked to register several times to access similar areas of our site). Cookies can be thought of as "memory seats" that reside on your computer. They do not give us any personal information about you. Basically, they serve as reminders for our site as to areas that you have already visited so you don't have to fill out another form to access information. We also provide hypertext links to sites of our business partners and other relevant sites. We are not responsible for the content and experience you may encounter on these sites.
Email lists
We provide you with opportunities to subscribe to email lists. This is purely voluntary on your part and, we will only use your registration information to provide you with related information in which you may be interested. We will not give or sell this email list to anyone outside of DSI or our business partners. If you want to be removed from our mailing list, please send an email to the webmaster.
Data Security
We will take reasonable precautions to protect personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, these measures, standing alone, are not sufficient to ensure the security of your personal information. It is also important for you to guard against unauthorized access to your passwords and the unauthorized use of your computer.
Legally Required Disclosures
DSI will, when permitted or required by law or court order, collect, use and/or disclose personal information pursuant to procedures that do not require giving notice or acquiring consent from affected users. This may include, but is not limited to, circumstances under which we may be required to disclose personal information in connection with law enforcement investigations. Therefore, although we are committed to maintaining the privacy and security of your personal information to the extent possible, we cannot and do not promise that your personal information will always remain private.
Privacy Compliance and Enforcement
Your use of this site, contact with DSI , and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice If you have any concerns about the privacy or security of your personal information, please contact us at privacy@discovery-solutions.com. We will attempt to resolve your inquiry in a timely manner.
We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy when our business policy requires that we do so. Any updates will be posted on this site and will become effective as of the date of posting without prior or additional notice.
